Is it an emergency situation
that you would need
an oncall animal control officer
to go there?
Do you by any chance know if your parents
were married at the time of your birth?
She wants to speak about food tax.
Is the control box or open or missing?
So we just got a call from Boston Fire reporting a one alarm fire at 33
Browning Ave. in Dorchester,
and there’s no displacements
at this time.
Just wait one moment while I do
some research for you.
I’m going to open up a case for
the Parks Department. They deal with trees.
I got a call from Boston Police. The intersection of the VFW Parkway and LaGrange Street in West Roxbury.
The traffic signal is out.
I just want to confirm that you had it.
I have a constituent that’s asking about
road maintenance.  Is it OK if I put him through?
Is it a stray dog?
She said she couldn’t see a visible cause.
Like there was no down wires or anything.
But the whole block appears to be out.
Is it blocking both the roadway
and the sidewalk?
Constituent’s saying her landlord turned off
her electricity to her apartment.
She said that she’s going back and forth
with him. They’re in court
with something and she thinks
she turned it off on him.